theblogfarm.com 2014-11-05

# The Blog Farm | Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes what user information is collected by The Blog Farm.

The Blog Farm shall be referred to as TBF within this document.

**What information does TBF collect?**

TBF collects the ip and browser information from any entity registered to post or comment on our site. When registering, you may be asked to enter your name and a required e-mail address for password verification and other important agreed upon contact communications.

**Does** **TBF**  use cookies?

TBF does use cookies that allow continuous log-in access when ‘keep me logged in box is checked.

**Does  ** **TBF**  disclose information to outside parties?

TBF does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. TBF may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links:**

Occasionally, at our discretion TBF may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. TBF therefore has no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, TBF seeks to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only:**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions:**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at: [Terms and Conditions](http://www.theblogfarm.com/disclaimer/)

**Your Consent:**

By using any aspect of The Blog Farm website you consent and agree to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:  **

Changes to The Blog Farm’s privacy policy may take place at any time without prior notification required. Any future changes to the policy will be posted here.

  * ### Mena Ukodoisready

Mental meanderings, pet peeves, lighthearted, jokes, demented thoughts or cerebral engaging articles, you will find it here.

  * ### Digital Combat Soldiers

We began as a squad playing the game Delta Force. A game industry portal linking the latest news, reviews and previews.. all games.. all platforms!

  * ### Dennys People Watching

Watching Life unfold, observing everyone at work and at play, making our lives interesting: people in the news…

  * ### Chatter Busy

A blog about Show Biz…

  * ### 365 Days Of Balloons

A daily blog showcasing a new balloon design each day. Mot is a Professional Balloon Entertainer and Magician. He has been creating smiles with his kid safe and family friendly entertainment for over a decade now.

### [Spooky Soiree](http://spookysoiree.blogspot.com/ "Spooky Soiree")

Halloween How-To’s & Parties on a Budget!
